Manzanar War Relocation Center records, 1942-1946
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Relocation center newspapers
  - Manzanar, California
    - Manzanar Free Press., April 1942-October 1945; MICROFILM 04388; Digitized microfilm.; Entire run of the publication.
      - July 1942
        - Manzanar free press, July 29, 1942, 1942-07-29
        - Manzanar free press, July 31, 1942, 1942-07-31
      - August 1942
        - Manzanar free press, August 3, 1942, 1942-08-03
        - Manzanar free press, August 5, 1942, 1942-08-05
        - Manzanar free press, August 7, 1942, 1942-08-07
        - Manzanar free press, August 10, 1942, 1942-08-10
        - Manzanar free press, August 12, 1942, 1942-08-12
        - Manzanar free press, August 14, 1942, 1942-08-14
        - Manzanar free press, August 17, 1942, 1942-08-17
        - Manzanar free press, August 19, 1942, 1942-08-19
        - Manzanar free press, August 21, 1942, 1942-08-21
        - Manzanar free press, August 24, 1942, 1942-08-24
        - Manzanar free press, August 26, 1942, 1942-08-26
        - Manzanar free press, August 28, 1942, 1942-08-28
        - Manzanar free press, August 31, 1942, 1942-08-31
      - September 1942
        - Manzanar free press, September 2, 1942, 1942-09-02
        - Manzanar free press, September 4, 1942, 1942-09-04
        - Manzanar free press, September 7, 1942, 1942-09-07
        - Manzanar free press, September 9, 1942, 1942-09-09
        - Manzanar free press, September 11, 1942, 1942-09-11
        - Manzanar free press, September 14, 1942, 1942-09-14
        - Manzanar free press, September 17, 1942, 1942-09-17
        - Manzanar free press, September 19, 1942, 1942-09-19
        - Manzanar free press, September 21, 1942, 1942-09-21
        - Manzanar free press, September 24, 1942, 1942-09-24
        - Manzanar free press, September 26, 1942, 1942-09-26
        - Manzanar free press, September 28, 1942, 1942-09-28
      - October 1942
        - Manzanar free press, October 1, 1942, 1942-10-01
        - Manzanar free press, October 3, 1942, 1942-10-03
        - Manzanar free press, October 5, 1942, 1942-10-05
        - Manzanar free press, October 8, 1942, 1942-10-08
        - Manzanar free press, October 10, 1942, 1942-10-10
        - Manzanar free press, October 12, 1942, 1942-10-12
        - Manzanar free press, October 15, 1942, 1942-10-15
        - Manzanar free press, October 17, 1942, 1942-10-17
        - Manzanar free press, October 19, 1942, 1942-10-19
        - Manzanar free press, October 22, 1942, 1942-10-22
        - Manzanar free press, October 24, 1942, 1942-10-24
        - Manzanar free press, October 26, 1942, 1942-10-26
        - Manzanar free press, October 29, 1942, 1942-10-29
        - Manzanar free press, October 31, 1942, 1942-10-31
      - November 1942
        - Manzanar free press, November 2, 1942, 1942-11-02
        - Manzanar free press, November 5, 1942, 1942-11-05
        - Manzanar free press, November 7, 1942, 1942-11-07
        - Manzanar free press, November 9, 1942, 1942-11-09
        - Manzanar free press, November 12, 1942, 1942-11-12
        - Manzanar free press, November 14, 1942, 1942-11-14
        - Manzanar free press, November 16, 1942, 1942-11-16
        - Manzanar free press, November 19, 1942, 1942-11-19
        - Manzanar free press, November 21, 1942, 1942-11-21
        - Manzanar free press, November 23, 1942, 1942-11-23
        - Manzanar free press, November 26, 1942, 1942-11-26
        - Manzanar free press, November 28, 1942, 1942-11-28
        - Manzanar free press, November 30, 1942, 1942-11-30
      - December 1942
        - Manzanar free press, December 3, 1942, 1942-12-03
        - Manzanar free press, December 5, 1942, 1942-12-05
        - Manzanar free press, December 25, 1942, 1942-12-25
      - January 1943
        - Manzanar free press, January 1, 1943, 1943-01-01
        - Manzanar free press, January 6, 1943, 1943-01-06
        - Manzanar free press, January 9, 1943, 1943-01-09
        - Manzanar free press, January 13, 1943, 1943-01-13
        - Manzanar free press, January 16, 1943, 1943-01-16
        - Manzanar free press, January 20, 1943, 1943-01-20
        - Manzanar free press, January 23, 1943, 1943-01-23
        - Manzanar free press, January 27, 1943, 1943-01-27
        - Manzanar free press, January 30, 1943, 1943-01-30
      - February 1943
        - Manzanar free press, February 3, 1943, 1943-02-03
        - Manzanar free press, February 6, 1943, En, 1943-02-06
        - Manzanar free press, February 6, 1943, Ja, 1943-02-06
        - Manzanar free press, February 10, 1943, 1943-02-10
        - Manzanar free press, February 13, 1943, 1943-02-13
        - Manzanar free press, February 17, 1943, 1943-02-17
        - Manzanar free press, February 20, 1943, 1943-02-20
        - Manzanar free press, February 24, 1943, 1943-02-24
        - Manzanar free press, February 27, 1943, 1943-02-27
      - March 1943
        - Manzanar free press, March 3, 1943, 1943-03-03
        - Manzanar free press, March 6, 1943, 1943-03-06
        - Manzanar free press, March 10, 1943, 1943-03-10
        - Manzanar free press, March 13, 1943, 1943-03-13
        - Manzanar free press, March 17, 1943, 1943-03-17
        - Manzanar free press, March 20, 1943, 1943-03-20
        - Manzanar free press, March 24, 1943, 1943-03-24
        - Manzanar free press, March 27, 1943, 1943-03-27
        - Manzanar free press, March 31, 1943, 1943-03-31
      - April 1943
        - Manzanar free press, April 3, 1943, 1943-04-03
        - Manzanar free press, April 7, 1943, 1943-04-07
        - Manzanar free press, April 10, 1943, 1943-04-10
        - Manzanar free press, April 14, 1943, 1943-04-14
        - Manzanar free press, April 17, 1943, 1943-04-17
        - Manzanar free press, April 20, 1943, 1943-04-20
        - Manzanar free press, April 21, 1943, 1943-04-21
        - Manzanar free press, April 24, 1943, 1943-04-24
        - Manzanar free press, April 28, 1943, 1943-04-28
      - May 1943
        - Manzanar free press, May 1, 1943, 1943-05-01
        - Manzanar free press, May 5, 1943, 1943-05-05
        - Manzanar free press, May 8, 1943, 1943-05-08
        - Manzanar free press, May 12, 1943, 1943-05-12
        - Manzanar free press, May 15, 1943, 1943-05-15
        - Manzanar free press, May 19, 1943, 1943-05-19
        - Manzanar free press, May 22, 1943, 1943-05-22
        - Manzanar free press, May 26, 1943, 1943-05-26
        - Manzanar free press, May 29, 1943, 1943-05-29
      - June 1943
        - Manzanar free press, June 2, 1943, 1943-06-02
        - Manzanar free press, June 5, 1943, 1943-06-05
        - Manzanar free press, June 9, 1943, 1943-06-09
        - Manzanar free press, June 12, 1943, 1943-06-12
        - Manzanar free press, June 16, 1943, 1943-06-16
        - Manzanar free press, June 19, 1943, 1943-06-19
        - Manzanar free press, June 23, 1943, 1943-06-23
        - Manzanar free press, June 26, 1943, 1943-06-26
        - Manzanar free press, June 30, 1943, 1943-06-30
      - July 1943
        - Manzanar free press, July 3, 1943, 1943-07-03
        - Manzanar free press, July 7, 1943, 1943-07-07
        - Manzanar free press, July 10, 1943, 1943-07-10
        - Manzanar free press, July 14, 1943, 1943-07-14
        - Manzanar free press, July 17, 1943, 1943-07-17
        - Manzanar free press, July 21, 1943, 1943-07-21
        - Manzanar free press, July 24, 1943, 1943-07-24
        - Manzanar free press, July 28, 1943, 1943-07-28
        - Manzanar free press, July 31, 1943, 1943-07-31
      - August 1943
        - Manzanar free press, August 4, 1943, 1943-08-04
        - Manzanar free press, August 7, 1943, 1943-08-07
        - Manzanar free press, August 11, 1943, 1943-08-11
        - Manzanar free press, August 14, 1943, 1943-08-14
        - Manzanar free press, August 18, 1943, 1943-08-18
        - Manzanar free press, August 21, 1943, 1943-08-21
        - Manzanar free press, August 25, 1943, 1943-08-25
        - Manzanar free press, August 28, 1943, 1943-08-28
      - September 1943
        - Manzanar free press, September 1, 1943, 1943-09-01
        - Manzanar free press, September 4, 1943, 1943-09-04
        - Manzanar free press, September 8, 1943, 1943-09-08
        - Manzanar free press, September 10, 1943, 1943-09-10
        - Manzanar free press, September 11, 1943, 1943-09-11
        - Manzanar free press, September 15, 1943, 1943-09-15
        - Manzanar free press, September 18, 1943, 1943-09-18
        - Manzanar free press, September 22, 1943, 1943-09-22
        - Manzanar free press, September 25, 1943, 1943-09-25
        - Manzanar free press, September 29, 1943, 1943-09-29
      - October 1943
        - Manzanar free press, October 2, 1943, 1943-10-02
        - Manzanar free press, October 6, 1943, 1943-10-06
        - Manzanar free press, October 9, 1943, 1943-10-09
        - Manzanar free press, October 13, 1943, 1943-10-13
        - Manzanar free press, October 16, 1943, 1943-10-16
        - Manzanar free press, October 20, 1943, 1943-10-20
        - Manzanar free press, October 23, 1943, 1943-10-23
        - Manzanar free press, October 27, 1943, 1943-10-27
        - Manzanar free press, October 30, 1943, 1943-10-30
      - November 1943
        - Manzanar free press, November 3, 1943, 1943-11-03
        - Manzanar free press, November 6, 1943, 1943-11-06
        - Manzanar free press, November 10, 1943, 1943-11-10
        - Manzanar free press, November 13, 1943, 1943-11-13
        - Manzanar free press, November 17, 1943, 1943-11-17
        - Manzanar free press, November 20, 1943, 1943-11-20
        - Manzanar free press, November 24, 1943, 1943-11-24
        - Manzanar free press, November 27, 1943, 1943-11-27
      - December 1943
        - Manzanar free press, December 1, 1943, 1943-12-01
        - Manzanar free press, December 4, 1943, 1943-12-04
        - Manzanar free press, December 8, 1943, 1943-12-08
        - Manzanar free press, December 11, 1943, 1943-12-11
        - Manzanar free press, December 15, 1943, 1943-12-15
        - Manzanar free press, December 18, 1943, 1943-12-18
        - Manzanar free press, December 22, 1943, 1943-12-22
        - Manzanar free press, December 24, 1943, 1943-12-24
        - Manzanar free press, December 30, 1943, 1943-12-30
      - January 1944
        - Manzanar free press, January 1, 1944, 1944-01-01
        - Manzanar free press, January 5, 1944, 1944-01-05
        - Manzanar free press, January 8, 1944, 1944-01-08
        - Manzanar free press, January 12, 1944, 1944-01-12
        - Manzanar free press, January 15, 1944, 1944-01-15
        - Manzanar free press, January 19, 1944, 1944-01-19
        - Manzanar free press, January 22, 1944, 1944-01-22
        - Manzanar free press, January 26, 1944, 1944-01-26
        - Manzanar free press, January 29, 1944, 1944-01-29
      - February 1944
        - Manzanar free press, February 2, 1944, 1944-02-02
        - Manzanar free press, February 5, 1944, 1944-02-05
        - Manzanar free press, February 9, 1944, 1944-02-09
        - Manzanar free press, February 12, 1944, 1944-02-12
        - Manzanar free press, February 16, 1944, 1944-02-16
        - Manzanar free press, February 19, 1944, 1944-02-19
        - Manzanar free press, February 23, 1944, 1944-02-23
        - Manzanar free press, February 26, 1944, 1944-02-26
      - March 1944
        - Manzanar free press, March 1, 1944, 1944-03-01
        - Manzanar free press, March 4, 1944, 1944-03-04
        - Manzanar free press, March 8, 1944, 1944-03-08
        - Manzanar free press, March 11, 1944, 1944-03-11
        - Manzanar free press, March 15, 1944, 1944-03-15
        - Manzanar free press, March 18, 1944, 1944-03-18
        - Manzanar free press, March 22, 1944, 1944-03-22
        - Manzanar free press, March 25, 1944, 1944-03-25
        - Manzanar free press, March 29, 1944, 1944-03-29
      - April 1944
        - Manzanar free press, April 1, 1944, 1944-04-01
        - Manzanar free press, April 5, 1944, 1944-04-05
        - Manzanar free press, April 8, 1944, 1944-04-08
        - Manzanar free press, April 12, 1944, 1944-04-12
        - Manzanar free press, April 15, 1944, 1944-04-15
        - Manzanar free press, April 19, 1944, 1944-04-19
        - Manzanar free press, April 22, 1944, 1944-04-22
        - Manzanar free press, April 26, 1944, 1944-04-26
        - Manzanar free press, April 29, 1944, 1944-04-29
      - May 1944
        - Manzanar free press, May 3, 1944, 1944-05-03
        - Manzanar free press, May 6, 1944, 1944-05-06
        - Manzanar free press, May 10, 1944, 1944-05-10
        - Manzanar free press, May 13, 1944, 1944-05-13
        - Manzanar free press, May 17, 1944, 1944-05-17
        - Manzanar free press, May 20, 1944, 1944-05-20
        - Manzanar free press, May 24, 1944, 1944-05-24
        - Manzanar free press, May 27, 1944, 1944-05-27
        - Manzanar free press, May 31, 1944, 1944-05-31
      - June 1944
        - Manzanar free press, June 3, 1944, 1944-06-03
        - Manzanar free press, June 7, 1944, 1944-06-07
        - Manzanar free press, June 10, 1944, 1944-06-10
        - Manzanar free press, June 14, 1944, 1944-06-14
        - Manzanar free press, June 17, 1944, 1944-06-17
        - Manzanar free press, June 21, 1944, 1944-06-21
        - Manzanar free press, June 24, 1944, 1944-06-24
        - Manzanar free press, June 28, 1944, 1944-06-28
      - July 1944
        - Manzanar free press, July 1, 1944, 1944-07-01
        - Manzanar free press, July 5, 1944, 1944-07-05
        - Manzanar free press, July 8, 1944, 1944-07-08
        - Manzanar free press, July 12, 1944, 1944-07-12
        - Manzanar free press, July 15, 1944, 1944-07-15
        - Manzanar free press, July 19, 1944, 1944-07-19
        - Manzanar free press, July 22, 1944, 1944-07-22
        - Manzanar free press, July 26, 1944, 1944-07-26
        - Manzanar free press, July 29, 1944, 1944-07-29
      - August 1944
        - Manzanar free press, August 2, 1944, 1944-08-02
        - Manzanar free press, August 5, 1944, 1944-08-05
        - Manzanar free press, August 9, 1944, 1944-08-09
        - Manzanar free press, August 12, 1944, 1944-08-12
        - Manzanar free press, August 16, 1944, 1944-08-16
        - Manzanar free press, August 19, 1944, 1944-08-19
        - Manzanar free press, August 23, 1944, 1944-08-23
        - Manzanar free press, August 26, 1944, 1944-08-26
        - Manzanar free press, August 30, 1944, 1944-08-30
      - September 1944
        - Manzanar free press, September 2, 1944, 1944-09-02
        - Manzanar free press, September 6, 1944, 1944-09-06
        - Manzanar free press, September 13, 1944, 1944-09-13
        - Manzanar free press, September 16, 1944, 1944-09-16
        - Manzanar free press, September 20, 1944, 1944-09-20
        - Manzanar free press, September 23, 1944, 1944-09-23
        - Manzanar free press, September 27, 1944, 1944-09-27
        - Manzanar free press, September 30, 1944, 1944-09-30
      - October 1944
        - Manzanar free press, October 4, 1944, 1944-10-04
        - Manzanar free press, October 7, 1944, 1944-10-07
        - Manzanar free press, October 11, 1944, 1944-10-11
        - Manzanar free press, October 14, 1944, 1944-10-14
        - Manzanar free press, October 18, 1944, 1944-10-18
        - Manzanar free press, October 21, 1944, 1944-10-21
        - Manzanar free press, October 25, 1944, 1944-10-25
        - Manzanar free press, October 28, 1944, 1944-10-28
      - November 1944
        - Manzanar free press, November 1, 1944, 1944-11-01
        - Manzanar free press, November 4, 1944, 1944-11-04
        - Manzanar free press, November 8, 1944, 1944-11-08
        - Manzanar free press, November 11, 1944, 1944-11-11
        - Manzanar free press, November 15, 1944, 1944-11-15
        - Manzanar free press, November 18, 1944, 1944-11-18
        - Manzanar free press, November 22, 1944, 1944-11-22
        - Manzanar free press, November 25, 1944, 1944-11-25
        - Manzanar free press, November 29, 1944, 1944-11-29
      - December 1944
        - Manzanar free press, December 2, 1944, 1944-12-02
        - Manzanar free press, December 6, 1944, 1944-12-06
        - Manzanar free press, December 9, 1944, 1944-12-09
        - Manzanar free press, December 13, 1944, 1944-12-13
        - Manzanar free press, December 16, 1944, 1944-12-16
        - Manzanar free press, December 18, 1944, 1944-12-18
        - Manzanar free press, December 20, 1944, 1944-12-20
        - Manzanar free press, December 23, 1944, 1944-12-23
        - Manzanar free press, December 30, 1944, 1944-12-30
      - January 1945
        - Manzanar free press, January 1, 1945, 1945-01-01
        - Manzanar free press, January 3, 1945, 1945-01-03
        - Manzanar free press, January 6, 1945, 1945-01-06
        - Manzanar free press, January 6, 1945, 1945-01-06
        - Manzanar free press, January 10, 1945, 1945-01-10
        - Manzanar free press, January 13, 1945, 1945-01-13
        - Manzanar free press, January 17, 1945, 1945-01-17
        - Manzanar free press, January 20, 1945, 1945-01-20
        - Manzanar free press, January 24, 1945, 1945-01-24
        - Manzanar free press, January 27, 1945, 1945-01-27
        - Manzanar free press, January 31, 1945, 1945-01-31
      - February 1945
        - Manzanar free press, February 3, 1945, 1945-02-03
        - Manzanar free press, February 7, 1945, 1945-02-07
        - Manzanar free press, February 10, 1945, 1945-02-10
        - Manzanar free press, February 14, 1945, 1945-02-14
        - Manzanar free press, February 17, 1945, 1945-02-17
        - Manzanar free press, February 21, 1945, 1945-02-21
        - Manzanar free press, February 24, 1945, 1945-02-24
        - Manzanar free press, February 28, 1945, 1945-02-28
      - March 1945
        - Manzanar free press, March 3, 1945, 1945-03-03
        - Manzanar free press, March 7, 1945, 1945-03-07
        - Manzanar free press, March 9, 1945, 1945-03-09
        - Manzanar free press, March 10, 1945, 1945-03-10
        - Manzanar free press, March 14, 1945, 1945-03-14
        - Manzanar free press, March 17, 1945, 1945-03-17
        - Manzanar free press, March 21, 1945, 1945-03-21
        - Manzanar free press, March 24, 1945, 1945-03-24
        - Manzanar free press, March 28, 1945, 1945-03-28
        - Manzanar free press, March 31, 1945, 1945-03-31
      - April 1945
        - Manzanar free press, April 4, 1945, 1945-04-04
        - Manzanar free press, April 7, 1945, 1945-04-07
        - Manzanar free press, April 11, 1945, 1945-04-11
        - Manzanar free press, April 14, 1945, 1945-04-14
        - Manzanar free press, April 14, 1945, 1945-04-14
        - Manzanar free press, April 18, 1945, 1945-04-18
        - Manzanar free press, April 21, 1945, 1945-04-21
        - Manzanar free press, April 25, 1945, 1945-04-25
        - Manzanar free press, April 28, 1945, 1945-04-28
      - May 1945
        - Manzanar free press, May 2, 1945, 1945-05-02
        - Manzanar free press, May 5, 1945, 1945-05-05
        - Manzanar free press, May 9, 1945, 1945-05-09
        - Manzanar free press, May 12, 1945, 1945-05-12
        - Manzanar free press, May 16, 1945, 1945-05-16
        - Manzanar free press, May 19, 1945, 1945-05-19
        - Manzanar free press, May 23, 1945, 1945-05-23
        - Manzanar free press, May 26, 1945, 1945-05-26
        - Manzanar free press, May 30, 1945, 1945-05-30
      - June 1945
        - Manzanar free press, June 2, 1945, 1945-06-02
        - Manzanar free press, June 6, 1945, 1945-06-06
        - Manzanar free press, June 9, 1945, 1945-06-09
        - Manzanar free press, June 13, 1945, 1945-06-13
        - Manzanar free press, June 16, 1945, 1945-06-16
        - Manzanar free press, June 20, 1945, 1945-06-20
        - Manzanar free press, June 23, 1945, 1945-06-23
        - Manzanar free press, June 27, 1945, 1945-06-27
        - Manzanar free press, June 30, 1945, 1945-06-30
      - July 1945
        - Manzanar free press, July 4, 1945, 1945-07-04
        - Manzanar free press, July 7, 1945, 1945-07-07
        - Manzanar free press, July 11, 1945, 1945-07-11
        - Manzanar free press, July 14, 1945, 1945-07-14
        - Manzanar free press, July 18, 1945, 1945-07-18
        - Manzanar free press, July 21, 1945, 1945-07-21
        - Manzanar free press, July 25, 1945, 1945-07-25
        - Manzanar free press, July 28, 1945, 1945-07-28
      - August 1945
        - Manzanar free press, August 1, 1945, 1945-08-01
        - Manzanar free press, August 4, 1945, 1945-08-04
        - Manzanar free press, August 8, 1945, 1945-08-08
        - Manzanar free press, August 11, 1945, 1945-08-11
        - Manzanar free press, August 15, 1945, 1945-08-15
        - Manzanar free press, August 18, 1945, 1945-08-18
        - Manzanar free press, August 22, 1945, 1945-08-22
        - Manzanar free press, August 25, 1945, 1945-08-25
        - Manzanar free press, August 29, 1945, 1945-08-29
      - September 1945
        - Manzanar free press, September 1, 1945, 1945-09-01
        - Manzanar free press, September 5, 1945, 1945-09-05
        - Manzanar free press, September 8, 1945, 1945-09-08
        - Manzanar free press, September 14, 1945, 1945-09-14
        - Manzanar free press, September 21, 1945, 1945-09-21
        - Manzanar free press, September 28, 1945, 1945-09-28
      - October 1945
        - Manzanar free press, October 5, 1945, 1945-10-05
        - Manzanar free press, October 12, 1945, 1945-10-12
        - Manzanar free press, October 19, 1945, 1945-10-19
    - Manzanar Free Press., April-December 1942; 1 bound volume. (Box 76)
    - Manzanar Free Press., April 1942-December 1943; 1 bound volume. (Box 77)
    - Manzanar Free Press., January 1-June 28, 1944; 1 bound volume. (Box 78)
    - Manzanar Free Press., July 1944-June 1945; 1 bound volume. (Box 76)
    - Manzanar Free Press and Manzanar Free Press Supplements., July-September 1945; 1 bound volume. (Box 78)
    - Manzanar Free Press., April 1942-October 1945; Unbound.; [duplicated in copies of Manzanar Free Press in Boxes 76-78.] (Box 106)
  - Newell, California
    - Newell Star., March 1944-March 1946; 1 bound volume. (Box 101)
    - Tulean Dispatch., June 1942-November 1943; 2 bound volumes. (Box 100, 104)
    - Tulean Dispatch., July 1-September 8, 1943; [duplicated in bound volumes in Boxes 97, 100 & 104.] (Box 61)
    - Tulean Dispatch Magazine., 1942-1943; 1 bound volume. (Box 97)
  - Tanforan, California
    - Tanforan Totalizer (weekly)., May 23-September 12, 1942 (Box 61)
  - Amache, Colorado
    - Granada Pioneer., October 1942-September 1945; 4 bound volumes. (Box 80-83)
  - Topaz, Utah
    - Co-op News., May 1943-January 1954; 1 bound volume. (Box 97)
    - Topaz Times., September 1942-August 1945; 5 bound volumes. (Box 90-92)
  - Heart Mountain, Wyoming
    - Heart Mountain Sentinel., October 1942-July 1945; 2 bound volumes. (Box 98-99)
    - Heart Mountain Sentinel Supplements., August 1942-June 1945; 1 bound volume. (Box 100)
- Miscellaneous publications and documents re: Japanese Americans during World War II
  Includes the subject of evacuation, relocation, resettlement.
  - Rohwer, Arkansas. Miscellaneous documents, including Rohwer Cooperative Enterprises operating statements., Sept. 1942-July 1944 (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous center publications., (unsorted) (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous publications., (unsorted) (Box 62-63)
    Included are journal articles, reprints, monographs, newspapers, and U.S. government documents, the majority of which belonged to Ralph Merritt, Project Director at Manzanar.
    Note: Copies of most of these items are accessible in the California Ephemera Collection (Collection 200), Boxes 41 and 42. See "Japanese in California."